Walt Kuhn Family Papers and Armory Show
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
- Walt Kuhn Family Papers, 1859-1978, Series 4:; (Box 3-26, 32-35, OV 39-55; 25.8 linear feet)
  - Printed Materials, 1908-1987, 4.9:; (Box 20-23, 34, OV 40, 46-47; 3.9 linear feet)
    - Promotional Ephemera (Box 22)
      - Circus Posters, undated, (Oversized material housed in OV 47) (Box 22, Folder 28)
      - Other Subjects, 1925-1968, undated, (5 folders) (Box 23, Folder 1-5)
    - Postcards, undated, (2 folders) (Box 23, Folder 6-7)
    - Sheet Music, 1888-1928, 1939-1940, undated, (3 folders; oversized material housed in Box 34) (Box 23, Folder 8-10)
    - Social Invitations and Announcements, 1929-1951, undated (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Oversized Magazine Article by Walt Kuhn, (Oversized material scanned with Box 20, F1) (Box 34)
    - Oversized Other Magazines, Newsletters, and Bulletins, (Oversized material from Boxes 22, F18-20) (Box 34)
    - Oversized Other Reproductions of Kuhn Artwork, (Oversized material from Box 22, F21) (Box 34)
    - Oversized Sheet Music, (Oversized material from Box 23, F8) (Box 34)
    - Oversized Blueprints of the Mrs. C.C. Rumsey Residence, (Oversized material from Box 20, F8) (Box OV 40)
    - Oversized Clippings, (Oversized material from Box 21 and Box 22) (Box OV 46)
    - Oversized Exhibition Ephemera, (Oversized material from Box 22, F10) (Box OV 46))
    - Oversized Circus Posters, (Oversized material from Box 22, F28) (Box OV 47)
  - Artwork, 1906-1952, 4.10:; (Box 23, 32, OV 48-54; 1.2 linear feet)
    This series contains original drawings, sketches, and prints created by Walt Kuhn. See also Series 4.11: Photographs and Scrapbooks, for addtional artwork in scrapbooks.
    Cartoons include bird cartoons published in Life and in the book A Little Bird Told Me (1908, see Printed Materials), personal cartoons by Vera and Walt Kuhn depicting themselves, and one sketch of the Kuhns attributed to the cartoonist Oscar Edward Cesare. Two sketchbooks from Kuhn's trips to the Western United States are found, as well as Kuhn family Christmas cards, with Walt Kuhn's linotype prints of western scenes. Kuhn's ongoing interest in the circus is seen in his notes, sketches, and ink drawings of clown acts from 1941, accompanied by a short essay by Kuhn entitled "Plan to Revitalize the Clown and Fun Problem of the Circus." Folders containing miscellaneous artwork include rough sketches and designs, as well as finished drawings and cartoons, mostly undated.
    Illustrated letters, sketches, and cartoons are scattered throughout the collection. See individual series descriptions for more details. Copies of artwork in this series are marked as such and filed alongside originals. Reproductions of additional artwork are filed in Provenance Files and Photographs and Scrapbooks.
    The bulk of this series has been scanned. Only a sample of original Drawings for Life has been scanned due to copyright statements giving reproduction rights to Life Publishing Company.
    - Original Drawings for Life, circa 1906-1912, undated, (partially scanned; oversized material housed in OV 48-54) (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Personal Cartoons, 1909-1910 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Sketchbooks from Trips to the Western U.S., 1928, 1936 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Walt Kuhn Christmas Cards (Box 23)
      - Original Drawings, 1938, 1947, undated (Box 23, Folder 15)
      - Hand-Colored and 2-color Prints, 1931-1955, undated (Box 23, Folder 16)
      - Duplicates, 1933-1952, undated (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Clown Act Sketches, Notes, and Watercolor Drawings, circa 1941, (4 folders) (Box 23, Folder 18-21)
    - Miscellaneous Original Sketches, Drawings, and Cartoons, 1929-1947, undated, (2 folders; oversized material housed in Box 32) (Box 23, Folder 22-23)
    - Miscellaneous Original Sketches, Drawings, and Cartoons, Copy, undated (Box 23, Folder 24)
    - Prints, 1928, undated, (Oversized material housed in Box 32) (Box 23, Folder 25)
    - The Hunt (Paper Toy Figures), circa 1920 (Box 23, Folder 26)
    - Costume Crest by Walt Kuhn, undated (Box 23, Folder 27)
    - Reproductions of Early Cartoons by Walt Kuhn, 1906, 1937, undated (Box 23, Folder 28)
    - Artwork by Others (Box 23)
      - 17th Century German Engraving, undated (Box 23, Folder 29)
      - Heirich von Zügel Sketch, undated (Box 23, Folder 30)
      - Jules Pascin Portrait of Walt Kuhn (reproduction of 1916 drawing), 1940 (Box 23, Folder 31)
      - Patsy Santo Painting and Tracings, 1940, undated (Box 23, Folder 32)
      - Brenda Kuhn Painting, 1922 (Box 23, Folder 33)
      - Brenda Kuhn Scrapbook, 1934-1935 (Box 23, Folder 34)
        (includes one sketch by Walt Kuhn)
    - Oversized Miscellaneous Sketch, (Oversized material scanned with Box 23, F22) (Box 32)
    - Oversized Prints, (Oversized material scanned with Box 23, F25) (Box 32)
    - Oversized Original Drawings for Life, (Oversized material scanned with Box 23, F12) (Box OV 48-54)
  - Photographs and Scrapbooks, 1859-1978, 4.11:; (Box 23-26, OV 55; 3.5 linear feet)
    This series contains individual photographs, notes, photograph albums, and scrapbooks of photographs and other materials, which depict Walt Kuhn, his family, friends and colleagues, homes and studios, art school, travel in the U.S. and Europe, works of art, and other miscellany.
    Among the persons pictured are Walt, Vera, and Brenda Kuhn, LaSalle Spier, John Quinn, Frederick James Gregg, George Overbury "Pop" Hart, Gus Mager, William and Edith Glackens and family, Pablo Picasso, Cecil Howard, Jo Davidson, W. Averell and Marie Harriman, Gary Cooper, Otis Oldfield, Lily Cushing Emmet, Patsy Santo, and many of Kuhn's models. Also included are portraits of Kuhn by Frederic D. Pangborn and Edward Weston.
    Scrapbooks (Volumes 5, 6, and 7) contain photographs, illustrated letters by Walt and Vera Kuhn, postcards to Vera's parents, real photo postcards, reproductions of early artwork of Walt Kuhn, and other ephemera. Illustrations depict Kit Kat Balls, the 23rd St. studio, and Fort Lee, NJ among other subjects. Many of the people and places depicted in albums and scrapbooks are also depicted in individual photographs, which are arranged within broad subject headings.
    Selected subjects are noted in the inventory list, below. Additional photographs are scattered throughout the collection. Additional scrapbooks can be found among Armory Show Records, Kit Kat Club and Penguin Club Records, and Other Projects. Additional illustrated letters are found in Armory Show Records, Walt Kuhn Letters to Family, and Artwork. Refer to individual series descriptions for more details.
    The bulk of this series has been scanned with the exception of negatives, copy prints, duplicates and photos of reproductions of artwork.
    - Photograph Albums and Scrapbooks (Box 23)
      - Volume 1: Illustrated Photograph Album, 1896-1901, (Oversized material housed in Box 35) (Box 23, Folder 35)
        (Brooklyn NY bicycle shop; homes; Paris art school)
      - Volume 1: Illustrated Photograph Album, Duplicate, circa 1901 (Box 23, Folder 36)
      - Volume 2: Photograph Album, 1899-1900 (Box 23, Folder 37)
        (California and Southwest)
      - Volume 2: Photograph Album, Duplicate Prints from Glass Negatives, 1899-1900 (Box 23, Folder 38)
      - Volume 2: Photograph Album, Original Glass Negatives, Copy Prints/Negatives, 1899-1900, (2 folders) (Box 23, Folder 39-40)
      - Loose Item from Volume 2, circa 1899-1900 (Box 23, Folder 41)
      - Volume 3: Photograph Album; Germany, circa 1901-1904 (Box 23, Folder 42)
        (Royal Academy in Munich, Wörth, Germany; Heinrich von Zügel; includes sketches)
      - Volume 3: Photograph Album; Germany, Duplicates, Negatives, and Copy Prints, circa 1901-1903, undated, (2 folders) (Box 23, Folder 43-44)
      - Loose Items from Volume 3, 1901-1902, undated (Box 23, Folder 45)
        (includes masquerade ball in Munich)
      - Volume 4: Photograph Album, 1904-1907, undated (Box 24, Folder 1)
        (Vera Spier and Friends)
      - Volume 5: Scrapbook, 1909-1912, undated, (partially scanned due to condition) (Box 24, Folder 2)
        (Walt and Vera Kuhn and friends; Fort Lee, NJ and 23rd St. studio; Kit Kat Balls; Blandford, Nova Scotia; photographs, drawings and illustrated letters to parents)
      - Volume 5: Scrapbook, Copy Prints, 1909-1912, undated (Box 24, Folder 3)
      - Loose Items from Volume 5, circa 1901-1937, undated (Box 24, Folder 4)
        (Royal Academy in Munich; New York School of Art class; Hackensack, NJ crowd; John Quinn; Vera Kuhn in costume; Kit Kat Ball drawing, original cartoons)
      - Volume 6: Scrapbook, 1909-1910, undated (Box 24, Folder 5)
        (23rd St. studio; photographs, drawings, and illustrated postcards)
      - Volume 6: Scrapbook, Copy Prints and Duplicates, undated (Box 24, Folder 6)
      - Loose Items from Volume 6, 1909 (Box 24, Folder 7)
      - Volume 7: Scrapbook; Nova Scotia, 1909-1910, (Oversized material housed in Box 35) (Box 24, Folder 8)
        (Kuhns' and Glackens' in Nova Scotia, photographs, postcards, ephemera, drawings)
      - Volume 7: Scrapbook; Nova Scotia, Copy Prints, undated (Box 24, Folder 9)
      - Volume 8: Photograph Album; Nova Scotia, 1912, (Oversized material housed in Box 35) (Box 24, Folder 10)
      - Volume 8: Photograph Album; Nova Scotia, Duplicates, 1912 (Box 24, Folder 11)
      - Volume 9: Photograph Album, 1911-1923 (Box 24, Folder 12)
        (Brenda Kuhn baby book; Ogunquit, ME; Fort Lee, NJ; Adirondaks)
      - Volume 9: Photograph Album, Duplicate Prints and Copies, 1912-1920, undated, (2 folders) (Box 24, Folder 13-14)
      - Loose Items from Volume 9, 1913-1923, undated (Box 24, Folder 15)
      - Volume 10: Photograph Album, circa 1911-1916 (Box 24, Folder 16)
        (Brenda Kuhn, Waldo Schmitt)
      - Volume 11: Photograph Album; Summers, 1924-1935, (not scanned due to format of album) (Box 24, Folder 17)
        (Kuhn family summer homes and studios)
      - Volume 11: Photograph Album; Summers, Duplicates and Copy Prints, 1927-1933, undated, (2 folders) (Box 24, Folder 18-19)
      - Volume 12: Photograph Album, 1928 (Box 24, Folder 20)
        (Prescott, AZ buildings; Walt Kuhn in Prescott; NYC buildings and parks)
      - Volume 13: Dismantled Photograph Album, 1931-1933 (Box 24, Folder 21)
        (Trips to Europe)
      - Volume 13: Dismantled Photograph Album, Duplicates and Copy Prints, 1931, undated, (2 folders) (Box 24, Folder 22-23)
      - Volume 14: Photograph Album; Central City, CO, 1936 (Box 24, Folder 24)
      - Volume 15: Photograph Album, undated (Box 24, Folder 25)
        (unidentified woman traveling in the Southwest circa 1910s)
      - Volume 16: Dismantled Scrapbook of Eloise Spaeth, 1944-1946, undated (Box 24, Folder 26)
        (copy prints, Walt Kuhn biographical)
    - Walt Kuhn (alone) (Box 24)
      - Portrait by Frederic D. Pangborn, circa 1904-1905, 1962, (Oversized material housed in Box 35) (Box 24, Folder 27)
      - Portrait by Frederic D. Pangborn, Copy Prints, undated (Box 24, Folder 28)
      - Portrait by Robert Waida, undated (Box 24, Folder 29)
      - Portrait by Robert Waida, Duplicates, undated (Box 24, Folder 30)
      - Portrait by Edward Weston, undated (Box 24, Folder 31)
      - Portrait by Edward Weston, Copy Prints, undated (Box 24, Folder 32)
      - Early Walt Kuhn Photographs, 1882-1911, undated, (Oversized material housed in Box 35) (Box 24, Folder 33)
      - Early Walt Kuhn Photographs, Copy Prints, undated (Box 24, Folder 34)
      - Later Walt Kuhn Photographs, circa 1927, 1948, undated, (Oversized material housed in Box 35) (Box 24, Folder 35)
      - Later Walt Kuhn Photographs, Negative and Duplicate, 1948, undated (Box 24, Folder 36)
    - Family (see also Albums, Homes and Studios, Travel) (Box 24)
      - Kuhn Family Photographs, circa 1865-1899, undated (Box 24, Folder 37)
      - Kuhn Family Photographs, Copy Prints, undated (Box 24, Folder 38)
      - Spier Family Photographs, 1868, 1881, undated (Box 24, Folder 39)
      - Spier Family Photographs, 1889, 1897, undated (Box 24, Folder 40)
      - Vier Spier (later Kuhn), 1901-1904, undated (Box 24, Folder 41)
      - Vier Spier (later Kuhn), Copy, undated (Box 24, Folder 42)
      - Vera Spier and Friends, 1898-1908, undated (Box 24, Folder 43)
      - LaSalle Spier (Vera Kuhn's brother) and Friends, 1909-1936, undated (Box 24, Folder 44)
      - Brenda Kuhn, 1935-1949, undated (Box 24, Folder 45)
      - Brenda Kuhn, Duplicate, undated (Box 24, Folder 46)
      - Brenda at Summer Camp, 1930 (Box 24, Folder 47)
      - Friends of Brenda Kuhn, 1927-1936 (Box 24, Folder 48)
        (Nanette Tarbox Beals)
      - Vera and Brenda Kuhn, 1940, 1951 (Box 24, Folder 49)
      - Other Family, 1938-1948, undated (Box 24, Folder 50)
    - Friends and Colleagues (see also Albums, Travel, and Homes and Studios) (Box 25)
      - Adler Family, Sonoma, CA, 1899-1901, 1921, undated (Box 25, Folder 1)
      - Walt Kuhn, Rudy and Helen Dirks, et al, 1900 (Box 25, Folder 2)
      - Walt Kuhn, John Quinn, et al at Wawbeek, NY, 1913 (Box 25, Folder 3)
      - Walt Kuhn, John Quinn, et al at Wawbeek, NY, Copy Negatives and Prints, undated (Box 25, Folder 4)
      - Walter Pach Portrait, undated, (Oversized material housed in Box 35) (Box 25, Folder 5)
      - Walter Pach Portrait, Copy Prints, undated (Box 25, Folder 6)
      - George Overbury "Pop" Hart, circa 1915, 1926, undated (Box 25, Folder 7)
        (with Walt Kuhn, Gus Mager in Fort Lee, NJ; Coyesville, NJ; Mexico)
      - George Overbury "Pop" Hart, Copy Negatives and Copy Prints, undated (Box 25, Folder 8)
      - Lenna and Ira Glackens, 1925, 1939, 1940 (Box 25, Folder 9)
      - Otis Oldfield, George Fitzgerald, et al, 1931 (Box 25, Folder 10)
      - Lily Cushing Emmet and Family, 1939, undated (Box 25, Folder 11)
      - Alice Wadsworth and Walt Kuhn at Goodyear Home, 1940 (Box 25, Folder 12)
      - O. A. Renne, 1940s (Box 25, Folder 13)
      - Walt Kuhn with Bert Lahr, Ethel Merman, et al, circa 1947 (Box 25, Folder 14)
      - Walt Kuhn with Bert Lahr, Ethel Merman, et al, Duplicate, circa 1947 (Box 25, Folder 15)
      - Walt Kuhn and Frank Cullen, Stuart, FL, 1947, undated (Box 25, Folder 16)
      - Walt Kuhn and Frank Cullen, Stuart, FL, Copies, 1947, undated (Box 25, Folder 17)
      - Walt Kuhn with Neighbors, NYC, 1947 (Box 25, Folder 18)
      - Bert and Olive Taylor and Family, undated (Box 25, Folder 19)
      - Julie Millicent Ingersoll, 1948-1952, undated (Box 25, Folder 20)
      - Julie Millicent Ingersoll, Duplicates, 1951, undated (Box 25, Folder 21)
      - Others, 1930-1947, undated (Box 25, Folder 22)
    - Homes and Studios (see also Albums) (Box 25)
      - 23rd Street Studio, NYC, 1909 (Box 25, Folder 23)
      - Fort Lee, NJ, circa 1915-1918, 1935, 1964 (Box 25, Folder 24)
      - Fort Lee, NJ, Duplicates and Copy Prints, undated (Box 25, Folder 25)
      - Maine (Box 25)
        (Ogunquit and Cape Neddick homes, towns, Kuhn family)
        - Maine, 1926-1927 (Box 25, Folder 26)
        - Maine, 1944-1946 (Box 25, Folder 27)
        - Maine, 1948 (Box 25, Folder 28)
        - Maine, 1950-1951 (Box 25, Folder 29)
        - Maine, 1960-1972 (Box 25, Folder 30)
        - Maine, Duplicates, 1944 (Box 25, Folder 31)
      - 14th Street Studios and Penguin Club, 1930 (Box 25, Folder 32)
        (exterior views)
      - 18th Street Studio, NYC, 1929, 1940-1948, (3 folders; oversized material housed in Box 35) (Box 25, Folder 33-35)
        (Walt Kuhn with models, including Helen Miller, George Fitzgerald, Ruth Johnston; 2 photo shoots for Collier's Magazine, including color transparencies and contact sheets; William Ward photographs of Walt Kuhn)
      - 18th Street Studio, NYC, Copy Negatives and Prints, Duplicates, 1940, 1978, undated, (4 folders) (Box 25, Folder 36-39)
      - Hotel Albert Apartment, NYC, 1941-1949, undated (Box 25, Folder 40)
      - Hotel Albert Apartment, NYC, Duplicates, 1949 (Box 25, Folder 41)
      - Summer Studio at Lake Buel, Great Barrington, MA, 1941-1942, (3 folders) (Box 25, Folder 42-44)
        (Walt Kuhn, Ruth Johnston, Paul Bird, Lily Cushing Emmet, Harry Whitney, Barnum and Bailey Circus in Pittsfield, MA)
      - Summer Studio at Lake Buel, Great Barrington, MA, Negatives, Duplicates and Copies, 1941-1942, undated, (3 folders) (Box 25, Folder 45-47)
      - Glackens Home, NYC, 1948-1949, undated (Box 25, Folder 48)
      - Glackens Home, NYC, Duplicates, 1948-1949, undated (Box 25, Folder 49)
      - Winslow Homer Studio Exterior, 1934, (copy prints only) (Box 25, Folder 50)
      - Homes of Family Members, 1925-1950, undated (Box 25, Folder 51)
      - Miscellaneous Family Places, 1930-1964 (Box 25, Folder 52)
        (Walt Kuhn birthplace and grave)
    - Travel (see also Albums) (Box 25)
      - Florida and Georgia, undated (Box 25, Folder 53)
      - Florida and Georgia, Duplicates, undated (Box 25, Folder 54)
      - Nova Scotia, 1912 (Box 25, Folder 55)
      - Northeastern U.S., 1917-1931 (Box 25, Folder 56)
      - Northeastern U.S., 1930-1934, undated (Box 25, Folder 57)
      - Northeastern U.S., Duplicates and Copy Prints, undated, (2 folders) (Box 25, Folder 58-59)
      - Europe, 1925-1933, (3 folders) (Box 25, Folder 60-62)
        (group photograph including Kuhn, Pablo Picasso, Jo Davidson, Cecil Howard and others in Paris; W. Averell and Marie Harriman at the Warburg estate in Paris)
      - Europe, Duplicates, 1925, 1931 (Box 25, Folder 63)
      - Western U.S., 1928-1937, (3 folders) (Box 25, Folder 64-66)
        (Harriman family, Sally Fox, Gary Cooper, Otis Oldfield; Prescott, AZ; California; Sun Valley Resort, Ketchum, ID)
      - Western U.S., Duplicates and Copy Prints, 1928, undated, (2 folders) (Box 25, Folder 67-68)
      - Photographic Postcards, undated (Box 25, Folder 69)
    - Miscellaneous Photographs (Box 25)
      - Unidentified Cartes de Visites, 1859-1883, undated, (2 folders) (Box 25, Folder 70-71)
      - A Cuban Trip and Letter to Vera Kuhn, undated (Box 25, Folder 72)
      - Kenyon Farm, Virginia, 1904 (Box 25, Folder 73)
      - Garibaldi Rebels in Juarez, Mexico, 1910s (Box 25, Folder 74)
      - Paris Nudes, 1920 (Box 25, Folder 75)
      - Show People, 1928, 1934, undated, (Oversized material housed in OV 55) (Box 25, Folder 76)
      - Show People, Copy Print, undated (Box 25, Folder 77)
      - New York City Scenes, 1929-1930, undated (Box 25, Folder 78)
      - Spain Scenes by Hal Kravis, 1936 (Box 25, Folder 79)
      - Stock Photographs of Venice, Italy, undated (Box 25, Folder 80)
      - Miscellaneous Unidentified Photographs, undated (Box 25, Folder 81)
    - Reproductions of Artwork (Box 25)
      - Vera Spier Art Jewelry Record Book, 1908 (Box 25, Folder 82)
        (Woodstock, NY studio)
      - Early Childhood Drawings, circa 1882, undated, (Oversized material housed in Box 35) (Box 25, Folder 83)
      - Cartoons for Wasp (1899-1900), undated, (Oversized material housed in Box 35) (Box 25, Folder 84)
      - Paintings, 1940-1947, undated (Box 25, Folder 85)
      - Paintings, Negatives, Duplicates and Copies, undated, (3 folders) (Box 25, Folder 86-88)
      - Drawings and Cartoons (including duplicates), 1941, undated, (2 folders; oversized material housed in Box 35) (Box 26, Folder 1-2)
      - Carvings, Collage, Sculpture, 1964, undated (Box 26, Folder 3)
      - Installation Views, 1946-1951, undated (Box 26, Folder 4)
      - Installation Views, Negative and Duplicates, 1946-1948 (Box 26, Folder 5)
      - Artwork by Others, 1934-1949, undated (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Oversized Photograph Album, Volume 1, (Oversized material scanned with Box 23, F35) (Box 35)
    - Oversized Scrapbook, Volume 7: Nova Scotia, (Oversized material from Box 24, F9) (Box 35)
    - Oversized Photograph Album, Volume 8: Nova Scotia, (Oversized material from Box 24, F11) (Box 35)
    - Oversized Walt Kuhn Portrait by Pangborn, (Oversized material from Box 24, F28) (Box 35)
    - Oversized Early Walt Kuhn Photographs, (Oversized material from Box 24, F34) (Box 35)
    - Oversized Later Walt Kuhn Photographs, (Oversized material from Box 24, F36) (Box 35)
    - Oversized Walter Pach Portrait, (Oversized material scanned with Box 25, F5) (Box 35)
    - Oversized 18th Street Studio, NYC Photographs, (Oversized material scanned with Box 25, F35) (Box 35)
    - Oversized Early Childhood Drawings, (Oversized material from Box 25, F83) (Box 35)
    - Oversized Cartoons for Wasp, (Oversized material from Box 25, F84) (Box 35)
    - Oversized Reproductions of Drawings and Cartoons, (Oversized material from Box 26, F1) (Box 35)
    - Oversized Photographs of Show People, (Oversized material from Box 25, F76) (Box OV 55)
  - Audio Recordings, 1965, 1969, 4.12:; (Box 26; 0.2 linear feet; 8 audio reels [circa 24 hours], 1 audio cassette)
    This series consists of 8 audio reels and 1 audio cassette. Reels 1 to 7 were made by Brenda Kuhn (1911-1993), daughter of Walt Kuhn, as she went through her father's papers from March to November, 1965, on the eve of their accession to the archives. In her recordings, she makes specific reference to letters, artwork, photographs, and other documents found in the Armory Show Records and Walt Kuhn Family Papers. In some cases, Brenda is able to provide witness accounts of persons and events documented in the papers. However, her comments often stray far afield of the papers and art historical figures known to her as she muses on the activities of her own life and her vocation as promoter of her father's work. On reel 6, side 2 she interviews Grace Jones Sarka, wife of Charles Sarka and friend of Walt Kuhn during his early years as an artist in New York.
    On reel 8, Brenda Kuhn's recollections are guided by Garnett McCoy, curator at the Archives of American Art, who interviews her about Walt Kuhn, the Kuhn family, and their contemporaries. Selected subjects on reels 1 to 8 are listed with the box inventory. All reels were recorded on both sides at a speed of 1 7/8 inches per second unless otherwise noted.
    The audio cassette was recorded on "Walt Kuhn Day" at Kuhn House in Cape Neddick, ME on the 50th anniversary of Walt Kuhn's death in 1969.
    This series has not been scanned.
    - Brenda Kuhn's Recordings, 1965, (1 of 4) (Box 26, Folder 7)
      Reel 1, First Side (Side 2): Brenda Kuhn discusses Walt Kuhn's letters of 1936 and vaudeville materials. Selected subjects include Union Pacific Railroad; Kuhn's contacts in Hollywood, CA; attitude towards homosexual men; his personality and manner of writing; the circus; Maine landscapes; the Kit Kat Club and Penguin Club artist's balls; burlesque; Vera Kuhn; Walt Kuhn's vaudeville productions.
      Reel 1, Second Side (Side 1): Brenda Kuhn discusses Vera Kuhn's date books and Kuhn family Christmas Cards. Selected subjects include a complete description of Christmas Cards and the disposition and exhibition of Walt Kuhn's paintings.
      Reel 2: Brenda Kuhn discusses Walt Kuhn letters from 1936 to 1946. Selected subjects include Walt Kuhn's stay at Lake Buel in 1941 and in Idaho in 1936; Averell Harriman's career; Kuhn's health, final illness, treatment, and death; Kuhn's cartoons; Kuhn's Cape Neddick, ME house; Mark Hanna; Ruth Johnston, Isabel and Paul Bird; Kuhn's oak tree paintings; Kuhn's anti-Semitism in letters; Jules Pascin.
    - Brenda Kuhn's Recordings, 1965, (2 of 4) (Box 26, Folder 8)